<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on Fayaz Mammoo</title>
    <link>https://rotatingbananas.com/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on Fayaz Mammoo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.124.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://rotatingbananas.com/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying SAP Extensibility: In-App vs. Side-by-Side</title>
      <link>https://rotatingbananas.com/docs/sap_extensibility_in_app_vs_btp-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rotatingbananas.com/docs/sap_extensibility_in_app_vs_btp-2/</guid>
      <description>When working with SAP solutions, one key question always arises: Should you extend In-App or go Side-by-Side with SAP BTP?
In-App Extensibility (SAP S/4HANA Cloud) In-App Extensibility focuses on enhancing the core SAP system directly. It’s ideal for quick, straightforward changes that don’t require external integrations.
Supported Patterns: Adapt existing Fiori UIs Create custom forms or email templates Add custom fields or business objects Create queries for analytics Define workflows and rules Enable process integration and data replication Examples Based on the Patterns: Modify Fiori UI: Add a “Delivery Priority” dropdown to the sales order app.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging AI in SAP with CAP and HANA Cloud&#39;s Vector Engine</title>
      <link>https://rotatingbananas.com/docs/leveraging-generative-ai-vector-engine-cap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rotatingbananas.com/docs/leveraging-generative-ai-vector-engine-cap/</guid>
      <description>Leveraging AI in SAP with CAP and HANA Cloud&amp;rsquo;s Vector Engine Artificial Intelligence (AI) is the most significant trend in 2024, and for good reason. The possibilities for users leveraging AI are immense, including generating code, AI-supported debugging, image and video generation, text generation, and process automation. Popular AI models like ChatGPT and DALL·E 3 showcase these capabilities. The real question for developers is how to harness the power of these models effectively.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing RAG with Generative AI Hub and Chroma Vector Store - Using Python SDK</title>
      <link>https://rotatingbananas.com/docs/leveraging-generative-ai-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://rotatingbananas.com/docs/leveraging-generative-ai-hub/</guid>
      <description>In the rapidly evolving world of artificial intelligence, generative AI technologies have become a cornerstone for innovative applications across various industries. As demonstrated in SAP&amp;rsquo;s recent tech bite, the Generative AI Hub on SAP Launchpad provides a robust platform for developers looking to explore and implement sophisticated AI-driven solutions. Here&amp;rsquo;s how you can leverage this powerful tool to enhance your applications and drive innovation.
Exploring the SAP Generative AI Hub The Generative AI Hub is designed to facilitate easy interaction with AI models through REST API calls from any programming environment, be it JavaScript, Python, or others.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
